What should I do?
どうすればいいですか?
That's fine.
いいです
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
I don't like trying it myself.
自分でやってみるの嫌なんですよ
So, touch Teach?
じゃあ、ティーチに触れる?
Don't you like doing it yourself?
自分でやるやつ嫌なの?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
What should I do?
どうすればいいですか?
So cute.
かわいいな
There was something.
あってあって
Well, let's touch it directly.
じゃあ、直接触っちゃおうか
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's because you have a small mouth.
口小さいからね
Beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱい
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Beauty.
美女
get nervous.
緊張する
Well then, do your homework.
じゃあ、手こっき
Can I talk to you?
話していいの?
amazing.
すごい
Have you ever had your breasts covered?
おっぱいにかけられたことある?
Not much.
あんまりないですね
Isn't it a little too much?
あんまりってことちょっとあるんじゃない?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Something has changed here.
なんかここ変わっちゃった
Because it was kind of cute.
ちょっとかわいかったから